This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
The White Beard Pirates have successfully pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines still block the path to Ace.
The battle is heating up.
After Luffy narrowly avoids a deadly encounter with Mihawk,
a battalion of human weapons known as pacifistas appear.
Look at the Bayhead! There's something out there!
What? What the hell are they?
Of course. I wondered when I'd get a glimpse of the government's human weapons.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? I'm confused.
The extermination strategy in action! The power of the pacifistas!
They all look just like the Warlord!
Kuma! No way! It's gotta be some kind of an illusion!
Well, this just got weird.
I think I know those guys.
They all look just like the Warlord.
Kuma! No way! It's gotta be some kind of an illusion!
Well, this just got weird.
I think I know those guys. They went on a rampage here a while back.
It's like having an army of Warlord's.
It's not scary, I mean, fuck!
And you fuck?
What, huh?
I think I know those guys. They went on a rampage here a while back.
But what do you think that it's gonna be like that?
Please go.
Mom, do you know that?
But there weren't that many when they attacked us.
Head office! Reporting in!
You gotta hear this!
Hello? Anyone?
So this one's gotta be the real Kuma, right?
I thought this was just some rumor.
But I've heard word that Dr. Vegapunk has been working on some kind of human weapon,
and he's been shipping out the prototypes to back up the Navy.
This could be them.
Well, that looks like a human weapon if I've ever seen one.
Sure, but why are they all Kuma?
Hey, Uncle!
This isn't looking like the plan we talked about.
I thought the pirates were supposed to be rounded up inside the bay,
so we could pick them off like fish in a barrel.
Why are they scattered all over the place?
That big guy with the axe, can you make out what he's saying?
I believe I've deciphered the Navy's plan.
They leaked the intel about the decision to expedite Ace's execution,
knowing that it would send us into a frenzy to save him.
After that, all they had to do was slowly back up their forces to fully lure us pirates into the bay,
and then they block off the bay head with their human weapons to close the trap.
Checkmate!
Now it all makes sense.
That's why Whitebeard ordered us to sink those Navy ships instead of advancing.
He saw through their plan.
If it weren't for him, we would have been trapped.
Yeah.
We can still attack from the front and the rear, even if they're not closed in the bay.
Stick to the plan and take down the Allied forces first!
Eliminate any pirate that's trying to stray from the enclosure to advance!
And there you go!
Got it!
And if our ships get caught in the crossfire?
Let's try to keep it to a minimum, okay?
So that's the plan, huh?
Then, time to work!
Quick!
Light up as many kumas as you want!
We'll knock them down!
No!
Please!
We'll knock them down!
Now fire!
Lots of pieces!
They vaporized them!
They're even willing to sacrifice their own men!
Don't lose faith!
March on!
Charge the plaza with all of your might!
The only retreat I know is death!
But I'll rescue Ace before they can send me down that road!
Everyone! Get off the ship now!
Destroy those mechanical monsters!
Yeah!
Have at you!
I shall not falter!
All units, get off the ice and defend the front line now!
Do whatever it takes to ensure the pirates don't reach the plaza!
Go! Fall back!
Hurry!
It's quite the unexpected pleasure to cross blades with the world's greatest swordsman!
Aren't I a lucky guy?
Your swordsmanship is of no small renown either!
We were certain to cross paths!
Now show me your skill!
I'm happy to give you a peek!
Rose Rondo!
Father Rondo!
What flowers would you like on your ground?
What flowers would you like on your grave?
Onward! Drive them in!
Hell no!
How's that feel?
There's no way those things are made of flesh and bone.
Well, they're obviously not human.
Then what are they?
Hey, what happened to the screen?
Struggle all you want, Whitebeard.
We still have the upper hand, ready to crush you.
As soon as every video feed has been cut, activate the encircling walls.
And once that's set, we will immediately execute Ace and round up all of our remaining enemies.
Yes, sir!
Move it!
They're about to kill Ace! I'd better hurry!
Sorry, back to square one!
Luffy, no!
Team Bay!
The Admiral's getting in on the fight!
Damn it!
Yet we must press on regardless.
We knew we would face insurmountable odds and undefeatable foes.
Them sending out their best only means we're too close for their comfort.
Time to die, son of dragon.
Hey, Ace's brother.
You're not running out of steam, are ya?
Huh?
Whitebeard's commanders!
We won't find any better backup than that!
You can't let one man halt your advance!
Now follow us!
Yeah!
Let's take him!
The Navy's pulling back, so now's our chance!
We're breaking through these bastards!
Ooh!
Looky here!
It's a real fight!
This game is done to deliver the
Commander Kuriel.
Look at that angry glower.
Do you really want to die with such a sour face?
You do realize you'll be buried in this bay if you stay here.
First, Ace will die.
And then your cronies will be trapped and wiped out.
I honestly couldn't care less about who's
going to win this war but watching Whitebeard die?
That's fun!
Pops and Ace won't die.
Not while I'm around!
Shall we put this match on hold?
Vista.
Much as I hate to, we do have other matters to worry about.
We've got to back down, so let's go, Smoker.
Didn't you hear the orders?
Yeah, I heard him.
Next time, Straw Hat.
Luffy, you can do it.
Stay strong.
Where the hell has the video feed been cut?
Sorry, sir.
It'll just be another minute.
Hey, have you found it?
Uh, no.
We're still searching, but it's just gone missing.
We're all set.
Hey, Gaffer, you're blocking the shot.
It seems like they've cut all the camera feeds except for one.
But what's with this stupid message?
Just show us already.
The camera's good to go.
Okay, then.
We're going live in five, four, three, two, one, action!
Hey, it came back on.
So, um, uh, sorry.
We apologize for keeping you waiting.
Wait, who is that talking?
Uh, we're live here at Marineford, surrounded by the dead bodies of pirates and marines.
They're doing a commentary?
Hey, what's going on down there?
What is this feed?
Wait, is that who I think it is?
Oh, it is!
I can't believe it's him!
He's been laying low for all these years, but...
He was a member of the legendary crew that served under Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates!
Huh?
Who is it?
Can it really be the renowned pirate, Captain Buggy?
Huh?
I'm sorry, did someone say my name?
It is classified information, but I admit it.
I am the legendary pirate!
Hey!
Hold it, Captain Buggy!
Stop!
You've got a nose blade!
What the hell is happening here?
How many times have I ordered you fools to catch this stupid video?
We can't move without world watching!
I understand, sir, but I'm afraid that the escaped prisoners have somehow managed to steal one of the video transponder snails from us!
What?!
How did you let this happen?!
Make up!
Ready to roll!
Alright guys, mark it!
Take two, in three, two, one, and...
Oh!
Is that who I think it is?
The legendary crew member of Gold Roger and the sworn brother of Shanks of the Four Emperors?
Could it really be the mythical pirate, Captain Buggy?
Did someone say my name?!
Stop those idiots right this second!
Whoa, that was close!
They bound us!
Run for it!
I just saw you get sliced in half by the infamous Hawkeye Mihawk!
But there's not even a scratch on you!
Who, me?
That's right!
I'm Buggy!
The living legend!
Blow them away!
I want them dead!
Cut back to the war, dammit!
Why are we getting video of this, moron?!
Go back to Ace!
We're gonna miss the execution!
I want to see that army apart while with you kumars!
They're driving us into a corner!
Stand tall, men!
We can't stop now!
Not until we know that Ace is safe!
Let's go!
Get ready!
Fire!
Hey, Pops!
Hey, Pops.
Oh, Squared. Good to see you're alive.
Yeah, barely.
Is that so? I was trying to reach you earlier.
How are things looking at the Bayhead now?
I'm sorry to say, but your allies were beaten pretty badly.
As for me, I only managed to get out of there through sheer luck.
Sengoku is one merciless bastard. He's pulling out every dirty trick he can think of.
Judging by your shift in tactic, I'm guessing you picked up on the Navy's plan.
I've known Sengoku and what he's capable of for a long time.
I see.
Little does he know it works in our favor for them to attack us from the rear.
I'm joining the fight. Our only chance is to keep pushing forward.
I couldn't agree more.
What's Squared doing up there?
You have 43 allied captains willing to die for you.
We're all in your debt, for now and for always.
We consider it a privilege to risk our lives for you and your crew.
And I'm grateful.
But this fight is...
Yes, I know.
This fight is to save a member of your family.
The great pirate Whitebeard is a man who would do anything for his family.
And your loyalty inspires loyalty.
That's why everyone followed you to this hell.
I do wish things were different.
But at the end of the day...
I'm not a part of your family.
It's not a part of your family.
Uh oh...
Massa Walla
Taliesa
Oh, thank you.
After witnessing Squard's betrayal against Whitebeard,
ripples of distrust and uncertainty spread within his alliance.
And yet Whitebeard's faith will not be shattered,
and it soon becomes clear that his allies are falling
into a clever setup launched by the Navy.
On the next, One Piece, Akainu's plot, Whitebeard entrapped.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.